Robin Holmqvist

Solidity Developer



Location: Skoghall, Sweden

discord: eros0524#5195,

Skype: live:.cid.af8c53398f48d6f4
Telegram: @@soliditydev001
Email: cryptodev000@gmail.com

Profile

I'm an enthusiastic, intelligent, productive and proficient Blockchain Developer specializing in Full Stack. I am an individual developer who is able to work well on his own initiative and can demonstrate the high levels of motivation required to meet the tightest of deadlines.

In the past five years, I have completed a number of Trading platforms exclusively for leading companies, and built a lots of NFT minting and Marketpace, DeFi, DEX and Dao projects on Ethereum, BSC, Polygon, Solana, Near, Avalanche Blockchain for friendly clients.

Skills

- ♦ Languages
 - JavaScript, TypeScript, Solidity, Rust, C++
- **♦** Frameworks
 - ReactJS, NodeJS, AngularJS, VueJS, NextJS, NuxtJS, Laravel, Codelgniter, Django, hardhat
- DevOps
 - Apache/Nginx server configuration, AWS services
- ♦ Blockchain
 - Solidity, Rust, NFT Minting and Marketplace, DeFi, Dex, Dao, Ethereum, Solana, BSC, Avalanche



Work Experience

Full Stack Developer at Visible One. Copenhagen, Denmark

Jan 2015- Nov 2017

- Developed E-commerce platform using React for fronted and NodeJS for backend.
- Built user Authentication and Authorization system using Auth0 API.
- Worked closely with the back-end team to display data using the Custom Components library Components, Redux, Redux Saga.
- Worked with backend engineers to optimize existing API Calls to create efficiencies by deprecating unneeded API calls.

Blockchain Developer at Visible One. Dubai, UA

Dec.2018 - Oct.2019

- Developed NFT Market place able to integrate with opensea.io
- Forked go-ethereum for new chain(ICICB chain)
- IPFS storage for content upload and implemented Firebase
- Implemented event monitoring on Web3.js
- Ruilt out a new version of front-end anniloation using React

Senior Blockcahin and Smart contract developer at NaNLABS. Paris, France

Dec.2019 - Jun.2021

- DeFi(Reflection token), Dex, Dao(Olympus,hectorDao), Swap, Tokenomics, Roadmap.
- NFT gaming and gambling, Casino, Metaverse(Three.js), Minting, Staking, Marketplace.
- Deep knowledge about blockchain system: Hashing, Mining, Merkle Tree, Proof of work, Proof of Stake, Chaining blocks etc..
- NFT Minting on Solana using Candy machine and anchor.

Achievements

- New Chain- https://icicbchain.com
 Vue 3, Tailwind CSS, Git, Web3, Golang, Rust
- NFT marketplace https://async.art
 React.js, API Integration, Git, Node.js, smart contract, NFT
- Finance app- https://distancelearningportal.com
 React.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Payment Integration, Unit Test, Git
- Openpetworld https://overworldlife.com
 React.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Web3, Solidity, NFT Mint, NFT Marketplace, Dex, Game
- Atari casino game on blockchain- atarichain.com
 React, Bootstrap, Web3, Solidity, NFT Mint, NFT Marketplace
- dex- https://julswap.com
 React, Material UI ,Web3, Solidity, NFT, smart contract
- Safulibero token https://safulibero.com
 React, Node.js, Bootstrap, Web3, Smart contract, Dapp, Dex, DeFi

Education

Dalarna University 2010 – 2014 Bachelor's degree of Computer Science